{
  "eachQuestionDuration": 60,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "What is the first step to initiate the installation process of software in Windows 10?",
      "options": [
        "Accept the End User License Agreement (EULA).",
        "Double-click the installer file with a \".exe\" extension.",
        "Choose the installation location.",
        "Create a desktop icon"
      ],
      "optionImages": [
        "https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQgByBT5IiAT_a2x9pUVb4VMoOrlzHH7Jrzj-HB5jzHlR4lNLMS"
      ],
      "answer": [
        "Double-click the installer file with a \".exe\" extension.",
        "Create a desktop icon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "What action triggers the User Account Control (UAC) prompt during software installation in Windows 10?",
      "options": [
        "Choosing the installation location",
        "Double-clicking the installer file.",
        "Accepting the End User License Agreement (EULA)",
        "Creating a desktop icon"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["Double-clicking the installer file."]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "Where can you find the option to accept the End User License Agreement (EULA) during software installation?",
      "options": [
        "In the installation location settings.",
        "After creating a desktop icon",
        "As part of the setup wizard steps",
        "Before providing a serial number"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": [
        "As part of the setup wizard steps",
        "Before providing a serial number"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "How do you typically complete the installation of software in Windows 10?",
      "options": [
        "By sorting applications by install date",
        "By confirming the uninstallation in a security prompt.",
        "By clicking \"Finish\" at the end of the installation wizard",
        "By providing a serial number during installation"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["By clicking \"Finish\" at the end of the installation wizard"]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "What is the first step to uninstall software in Windows 10?",
      "options": [
        "Selecting the application from a list.",
        "Opening the Windows menu and going to \"Settings.\"",
        "Confirming the uninstallation in a security prompt",
        "Scrolling through installed applications"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["Opening the Windows menu and going to \"Settings.\""]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "Where in Windows 10 settings can you navigate to view all installed applications for uninstallation?",
      "options": [
        "Privacy settings",
        "Irrigation",
        "Update & Security settings",
        "System settings"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["Apps settings"]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "How can you locate an application quickly for uninstallation in Windows 10 settings?",
      "options": [
        "By creating a desktop icon",
        "By sorting applications by install date",
        "By accepting the End User License Agreement (EULA)",
        "By double-clicking the installer file"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["By sorting applications by install date"]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "What is the final step to completely remove a program during uninstallation in Windows 10?",
      "options": [
        "Confirming the uninstallation in a security prompt",
        "Following any additional instructions",
        "Sorting applications by install date",
        "Providing a serial number"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["Following any additional instructions"]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "What action is required to confirm the uninstallation of a program in Windows 10?",
      "options": [
        "Creating a desktop icon\\",
        "Accepting the End User License Agreement (EULA)",
        "Clicking \"Uninstall\" after selecting the application",
        "Double-clicking the installer file"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["Clicking \"Uninstall\" after selecting the application"]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "questionImage": null,
      "question": "Which option is typically available after uninstalling a program in Windows 10 settings?",
      "options": [
        "Sorting applications by install date",
        "Confirming the removal of related files",
        "Double-clicking the installer file",
        "Accepting the End User License Agreement (EULA)"
      ],
      "optionImages": [],
      "answer": ["Confirming the removal of related files"]
    }
  ]
}
